练习 15-2：实际应用，总统候选人辩论。下面开始段落。
Exercise 15-2, Presidential Candidates' Debate. The President tomorrow night is
预计会在国情咨文中提出联邦补贴，
expected, in his State of the Union message, to propose federal subsidies to
help low-income families overcome the so-called digital divide. Is it an
appropriate use of government funds to hand out computers and provide internet
access to those who can't afford it? And if not, why not? We'll begin with Mr.
Keyes. I think this is another case where politicians try to jump on the bandwagon
of something that's going on in the economy so everybody's going to think that
they actually have something to do with the result when they don't. There is no
need for this. We are already seeing out there proposals for the distribution of
free PCs not based on some politician making a judgment and spending taxpayer
money, but based on the self-interest of those who are involved in a new world, a
new world in which participation is the key to profit, and in which there is
actually a strong incentive among those who participate in the private sector to
give access to individuals so that they can improve their opportunities for
profit, for information sharing. That's what has already been going on. It will
continue. There is no need for the government to pretend that it needs to
take leadership here. I think that's just political posturing. Senator McCain. I
believe that we do have a problem, And that is that there's a growing gap between
the haves and the have-nots in America. Those that are able to take part in this
information technology and those that haven't. We took a major step forward when
we decided to wire every school and library in America to the internet. That's
a good program. We have to have step two, three, and four, which means good
equipment, good teachers, and good classrooms. Now I wouldn't do it directly,
but there's lots of ways that you can encourage corporations who, in their own
self-interest, would want to provide, would receive tax benefits, would receive
credit, and many other ways for being involved in the schools and upgrading the
quality of the equipment that they have, the quality of the students, and thereby
providing a much-needed, well-trained workforce. Thank you. Mr. Forbes.